[♪ music ♪]
[♪ موسيقى ♪]
[Sam and Friends] Sam and Friends.
[سام وأصدقاؤه] (سام) وأصدقاؤه.
[brought to you] brought to you
[يأتيكم برعاية] يأتيكم برعاية
[by Esskay Quality] by Esskay.
[إيسكاي كواليتي] "إيسكاي".
[♪ music ♪]
[♪ موسيقى ♪]
The platter they're playing on this TV show
الأسطوانة التي يقومون بتشغيلها على هذا البرنامج التلفزيوني،
seems to have gotten stuck.
يبدو أنّها تعثّرت.
It's got a swinging beat but it's repetitious man.
إنّ لها إيقاع متغير، ولكنه مكرّر يا رجل.
Maybe if I just hit the television like this
ربّما لو ضربت التلفاز بهذا الشكل!
♪ Old black magic has me in a spell ♪
♪ السحر الأسود القديم أوقعني في شباك تعويذته ♪
that you weave so well ♪
الذي تُجيد حبكه ♪
♪ Icy fingers up And down my spine ♪
♪ تلك الأصابع الباردة التي تمرّ عبر ظهري ♪
♪ The same old witchcraft when your eyes meet mine ♪
♪ والسحر القديم المعتاد حين تلتقي عيناك بعينيْ ♪
♪ The same old tingle that i feel inside ♪
♪ هي نفس التنميلة التي أحسّها بداخلي ♪
♪ And then that elevator starts its ride ♪
♪ ثمّ يبدأ ذاك المصعد في رحلته ♪
♪ Down and down I go, round and round I go ♪
♪ يأخذني إلى الأسفل، يأخذني هنا وهناك ♪
♪ Like a leaf caught in the tide ♪
♪ كورقة أمسكت بها الأمواج ♪
♪ I should stay away but what can I do ♪
♪ عليّ أن أبتعد ولكن ما عساي أن أفعل ♪
♪ I hear your name, and I'm aflame ♪
♪ أسمع اسمك، فأكتوي باللهب ♪
♪ Aflame with such a burning desire ♪
♪ لهب! رغبة تحترق! ♪
♪ That only your kiss can put out the fire ♪
♪ قُبلةٌ منك فقط ما يُطفئها ♪
♪ You're the lover I have waited for ♪
♪ من أجلكِ يا حبيبتي التي طال انتظاري لها ♪
♪ You're the mate that fate had me created for ♪
♪ أنت الرّفيق الذي اختارني القدر لأجله ♪
♪ And every time your lips meet mine ♪
♪ وكلّما لامست شفتاك شفتاي ♪
♪ Baby down and down I go, All around I go ♪
♪ تأخذاني إلى أسفل السّافلين، تأخذاني هنا وهناك ♪
♪ In a spin, loving the spin I'm in ♪
♪ في دوّامة، وكم أحبّ الدّوامة التي أنا فيها ♪
♪ Under that old black magic called love ♪
♪ تحت رحمة السحر الأسود القديم الذي يُدعى بالحبّ ♪
♪ In a spin, loving the spin I'm in ♪
♪ في دوّامة، وكم أحبّ الدّوامة التي أنا فيها ♪
♪ Under that old black magic called love ♪
♪ تحت رحمة السحر الأسود القديم الذي يُدعى بالحبّ ♪
♪ In a spin, loving the spin I'm in ♪
♪ في دوّامة، وكم أحبّ الدّوامة التي أنا فيها ♪
♪ Under that old black magic called love ♪
♪ تحت رحمة السحر الأسود القديم الذي يُدعى بالحبّ ♪
♪ I should stay away but what can I do ♪
♪ عليّ أن أبتعد ولكن ما عساي أن أفعل ♪
♪ I hear your name, and I'm aflame ♪
♪ أسمع اسمك، فأكتوي باللهب ♪
♪ Aflame, burning desire ♪
♪ لهب! رغبة تحترق! ♪
♪ That only your kiss can put out the fire ♪
♪ قُبلةٌ منك فقط ما يُطفئها ♪
♪ You are the lover I have waited for ♪
♪ من أجلكِ يا حبيبتي التي طال انتظاري لها ♪
♪ You're the mate that fate had me created for ♪
♪ أنت الرّفيق الذي اختارني القدر لأجله ♪
♪ And every time your lips meet mine ♪
♪ وكلّما لامست شفتاك شفتاي ♪
♪ Baby down and down I go round and round I go ♪
♪ تأخذاني إلى أسفل السّافلين يا حبيبتي تأخذاني هنا وهناك ♪
♪ In a spin, loving the spin I'm in ♪
♪ في دوّامة، وكم أحبّ الدّوامة التي أنا فيها ♪
♪ Under that old black magic called love ♪
♪ تحت رحمة السحر الأسود القديم الذي يُدعى بالحبّ ♪
♪ In a spin, loving the spin I'm in ♪
♪ في دوّامة، وكم أحبّ الدّوامة التي أنا فيها ♪
♪ Under that old black magic called love ♪
♪ تحت رحمة السحر الأسود القديم الذي يُدعى بالحبّ ♪
♪ In a spin, loving the spin I'm in ♪
♪ في دوّامة، وكم أحبّ الدّوامة التي أنا فيها ♪
♪ Under that old black magic called love ♪
♪ تحت رحمة السحر الأسود القديم الذي يُدعى بالحبّ ♪
And now a word from our sponsor.
والآن، كلمة من رعاة البرنامج.
Folks, tonight I'd like to talk about—
في هاته الليلة يا رفاق أود أن أتكلّم عن—
Hold it! Stop the presses!
توقّف! أوقف المؤتمر الصّحفي!
Excuse me professor, but I'm in the middle of a commercial.
أعذرني يا أستاذ، ولكنّني بصدد تقديم إعلان تجاري.
Well, I've decided we're going to call off the commercial tonight.
لقد قرّرنا إلغاء الفقرة الإعلانية لهذه الليلة.
You're all getting sloppy on your delivery.
فقد بدأتم تتهاونون في خدمة التوصيل.
Come up here everybody.
اصعدوا إلى هنا جميعا.
The Esskay people aren't going to like this skipping.
أصحاب شركة (إيسكاي) لن يعجبهم تصرّفك.
All right now gentlemen. We've got a problem.
حسنٌ يا رجال، لدينا مشكلة هنا.
We're not getting the Esskay Quality story
لن نُذيع فقرة (إيسكاي كواليتي)
across to our audience. Here's a company
لمشاهدينا. هذه الشّركة
that's been turning out the finest quality products
التي قدّمت لنا منتجاتٍ عالية الجودة
for over 100 years, and what are we doing about it?
لأكثر من مئة عام، وماذا سنفعل حيالها؟
If you'd stop interrupting— >> Nothing!
إن توقّفت عن مقاطعتي— >> لا شيء!
Those listeners out there are doing the important thing
أولئك المستمعون يفعلون الشّيء المهمّ
when they shop. They're buying things
عندما يذهبون للتسوّق، فهم يشترون أشياء
for the most important people in the world, their family.
لأهمّ الأشخاص في العالم، عائلاتهم.
And that means they shouldn't be buying anything
وهذا يعني أنّهم لا يجب عليهم شراء أيّ شيء
but Esskay Quality products. Right?
ما عدا منتجات (إيسكاي كواليتي)، أليس كذلك؟
Right. >> All right then. Let's do a good job.
صحيح. >> حسنٌ إذًا. فلنبلي بلاءً حسنا.
Now try it Omar. And give us some gumption.
لتحاول الآن يا (عمر)، وأبهرنا بإبداعاتك.
I can't. Our time is up.
لا أستطيع، فقد نفذ الوقت.
[♪ music ♪]
[♪ موسيقى ♪]
[Sam and Friends brought to you]
[سام وأصدقاؤه يأتيكم برعاية]
[by Esskay Quality] By Esskay.
[إيسكاي كواليتي] (إيسكاي).